Kevin Towner

908.577.6666 · Kevintowner@gmail.com · kevin-t-b0960b96

Summary

I'm a web designer skilled in crafting intuitive UI and content management. I have two years of professional experience in designing website panel content, and content managing digital optimization assets. Looking to transition my career towards product design and user experience.

Career

AIG (Travel Guard) New York, NY

Web Designer

October, 2022 - Present

- Design and content authoring for high priority airline partners.
- * Ran several optimization tests for United Airlines and Spirit Airlines.
- Manage United Airlines Mobile App HTML trip insurance content.
- Mock up components and test factors for internal test design reviews.

AIG (Op Services) Berkeley Heights, NJ

Account Analyst

2019-2022

Documented Op Services processes, and assisted with quote preparations, policy endorsements and renewals, and insurance cancellation notices.

Business Services Associate

2017-2019

Processed quote requests and researched broker codes for appropriate underwriting assignments.

Hollister Co. Livingston, NJ

Store Manager 2014-2017

❖ Managed seasonal floorsets, visual merchandising, and in□store marketing placements.

Education

Drexel University

Master of Science in Human Computer Interaction

2024

Kean University

Bachelor of Arts in Criminal Justice

2014

Experience

UI Design, Prototyping, UX Research, Qualitative Research, HTML, CSS, LESS, Figma, Sketch, Competitive Analysis, A/B Testing, Multivariate Testing, Content Management, Adobe Experience Manager (AEM), Adobe Target, Artifacts Gathering, QA, Business Requirements, Content Authoring, Communication, Project Management